Now, I am up right now over $40,000 on
this juicy long trade. The setup was
given in advance in my community and I
let everybody know exactly when I was
taking the trade. And we have to talk
right now about what is going on with
the Bitcoin price because we are at a
crucial level. And when things are
boring, let's be honest, this is more
boring than watching paint dry. When the
price action squeezes together this
tightly and nobody's paying attention,
that is when the big moves happen. That
is when the big profits are made. And so
our job as traders is to be prepared for
the next move. And I'm going to be
walking through exactly how I'm trading
this and what I'm looking to happen in
the future, guys. So make sure to watch
until the end of the video. I'm going to
be walking you through the exact next
trade setups that I'm looking to put big
money on. And don't forget to like and
subscribe and click the bell for
notifications cuz it's the best channel
in the world. Do it right now.
>> Wait a second. Isn't this the guy that
paid Donald Trump $200 to try to get him
to say Bitcoin in the middle of one of
his speeches? Maybe that is true. But
I've also been able in the past 12 years
to pull myself up by the bootstraps and
go from a guy who had just graduated
with his degree in trans non-carbon
binary emission gender intersectionality
studies to this that you see today to
this that you see today. Kind of guy who
trades millions of dollars live on the
internet and publicly chat GPTs his P&L
from every single trade he's taken for
the entire year. So buckle up and get in
baby cuz if this ain't cringe then I
honestly don't know what is. Man, what a
loser I am. Huh? Okay, so right now the
charts are very boring, but they are
very simple and easy to understand.
First, we're going to ask ourselves the
question, is the macro Bitcoin bottom
in? Now, there is a case to be made that
the bottom of the bare market is in. How
could we make that argument? Right now,
we are printing on market cipher B on
the twoe time frame, a confirmed bullish
divergence on the two-week time frame.
What is a bullish divergence? The price
makes a lower low. The oscillator makes
a higher low. We saw this happen last
bare market bottom right at the low as
we came down below $17,000 to around
$15,500.
We got the confirmed bullish divergence.
The price is making a lower low. The
oscillator starts looking like this
juicy set of uneven butt cheeks. Big on
the left, skinny on the right. This
reason alone is why somebody could make
an argument that the bottom of the bare
market the lowest price is in. However,
we need to understand that going back,
and this is the Bitcoin all-time history
here, going all the way back to 2014,
the Bitcoin price does not bottom out
until at least 365 days after the
all-time high. So, we go back the last
three cycles here. I have, you can see
from the all-time high, the green line
is 365 days after and the past two
cycles pretty much to the day, the 365
day marker. That is the bottom. Happened
in 2019, happened in 2022. Now, that
365day marker for us is going to come in
in around the first or second week of
October. So, we still have a few months,
about 2 months until that bottom is
expected to begin. Something else that
every single Bitcoin cycle does is we
don't bottom out until we hit the 78.6%
Fibonacci retracement from the all-time
high. We did that in 2014. We did that
in 2019. We did that here in 2022. The
786 Fibonacci is this light blue line
that my mouse is on here. And so really,
we're looking if things are going to
happen the same way they happened
before. We're looking for the price to
bottom out around this area around this
time. This is actually still my
preferred target for Bitcoin. I just
want to say that we are printing a
signal on the oscillator that
historically has been the bottom. So,
right now it is a battle between the
signal on the oscillator versus the
4-year cycle. Is the 4-year cycle going
to continue as it has the last four
cycles? Well, obviously, we cannot know
that for certain. So, here's how I'm
playing this on the big time frames as
it pertains to buying Bitcoin on spot.
Now, let me just say I publicly went on
Twitter back in November 2025 when
Bitcoin was over $100,000 and I said I
sold 120K. I'm glad I sold. I am not
going to buy again until after we lose
$70,000. Check back in February to see
if I'm smart or not. And and by the way,
just so everyone knows, I literally
shorted the exact top of Bitcoin live.
Here's the dang position size from the
exact top. Told the community that I
shorted it. So, as I'm looking at the
spot Bitcoin right now from the top
where I took my short and even from
November when we were at $110,000
[clears throat]
and I told everybody, I'm not going to
buy until we're under 70K. We are down
right now from that top. We have come
down like 50%.
50%. What does this mean? It means right
now, no matter what, Bitcoin is half
off. If there's any other asset in life
that you find value in that you would
like to have and all of a sudden you
have an opportunity to buy it at 50%
off. Objectively speaking, that is a
good buy. So what I am doing right now
because of course in February my exact
prediction date is when we lost 70k when
we did that I am now partially in
Bitcoin on spot. I have allocated around
40% of the USDT 30 33% of USDT that I
have to buy Bitcoin into Bitcoin right
now. So right now I am exposed to
Bitcoin. And I think it's a good time if
you're not exposed to get exposed. Why?
Well, because if the bottom is in now,
[snorts] now you're exposed to the
market for the way up. If the bottom is
yet to be in, well, guess what? We can
DCA in this area right here and build up
a big position for the next bull market.
Remember, last bull bare market cycle
after a 50% drop that took us right here
to around $35,000. If you had bought
Bitcoin at $35,000, if you had bought
when we dropped again to $25,000 and
then bought again when we dropped to
$15,000 and you allocated in, guess
what? Now your average position is in
there at around $25ish,000.
And then you ride up and make 400% gains
in the bull market. So we're building a
position now at the lows because we know
based on the indicators, based on the
Fibonacci, based on the time frame, the
low is very close. And so for me,
because we can't overcertain, I don't
want to just make it a one-time thing. I
want to be allocate DCAing into Bitcoin
right now as we're approaching the low.
It may be already here so I can take
advantage of the price action in the
future. So that is how I'm currently
playing the market right now on Bitcoin.
Now, as far as what I'm looking for when
it comes to leverage trading, I believe
that there's plenty of opportunity
within this tight zone of consolidation
to take advantage of the move that is
inevitably coming within the next few
weeks or months. Inevitably coming. This
is the context in which we are looking
for setups right now. The Bitcoin price
is chopping around the fair value zone.
And so therefore, it is going to break.
It's either going to break to the upside
or to the downside. If it breaks to the
downside, the trade that I'm looking for
is going to be this. All right? I'm
going to be looking for a long position
to make a higher low. And I'm looking
then to shoot to the top of this range.
Why would I be looking for a trade like
this? Well, it's because we have the
potential of a shoulder, a head, and
then another shoulder. If we pull the
Fibonacci from the low to the high, you
see that we're coming in right between
the zone of the golden pocket, the 786,
and the macro value area low. And let's
not forget the fact that as we came down
and we did bounce from the macro
Fibonacci 618, the most reactive
Fibonacci level period is the 618. This
is the macro 618 from the bare market
bottom to the bull market top. And you
can see we have a bullish divergence
here. This bullish divergence is
happening at the bottom where as the
price is getting lower to a macro key
Fibonacci support, the oscillator is
getting higher. And you can see here
that we are printing a green dot as the
money flow is getting thicker. This is a
continuation pattern. And so if we are
gifted with a move down to $60,000, I
would absolutely look to trade this up
to around the $67,000 zone. Now, what if
we don't drop to the downside here? What
if we don't come down and take this
liquidity and bounce from key support?
What if we go straight up? Well, then we
also have two trading opportunities on
our hands. The first one obviously is
going to be a short trade, a fake out of
the highs of this range here. Basically,
people are going to get really bullish.
They're going to say, "Oh, we're going
back up to $75, $80,000. The bottom's
in." But guess what? The price can't do
it. The price comes up and chops around
here, and then eventually it comes right
back down. And so, of course, as we come
into this area, we need to be looking
for short trades. What would we look for
on our oscillator to get into a short
trade? We would look for the momentum
waves now to print the bearish
divergence. We would look for it to
print the upside down uneven butt cheek
pattern where this time the same lady
who was here getting us all bullish is
hanging upside down from the rafters.
Look, it's fall fun and games until this
lady starts hanging upside down from the
rafters. And what do you think is going
to happen? You think she can support
herself up there for long? No. So,
there's going to be a drop. Boom. Then
we could get a drop back down. Now,
let's say we don't get a drop back down.
Let's say we come up to the level and
instead of getting a fake out, what
happens is we break out or we get a back
test and then we hold this as support.
That actually then gives us another long
setup to look for. We can long the
support resistance flip here. Our stop
loss goes below wherever the back test
is and we can shoot up to the value area
high of this range, which is around
$73,000.
Those are basically the new trades that
I'm looking for. And of course, in the
Casper Crew VIP Discord, where you know,
look, I give the setups in advance. I
let people know when I'm taking the
trades, whether it be a swing trade,
like the long one we're in now, up 40
grand, or the scalp trade that we took
yesterday where we made like a couple
hundred dollar literally in a few
minutes. I do that at Jason
Casperrading.com to join the best
community in the world. Also, guys, I
want to let you know Bitbase is giving
away $500 a week. We're doing this
during my public live streams. All you
have to do is create an account using
the link in the description of this
video or the pinned comment to be
eligible to win $500 every single week.
Also, Blofin is giving away $2,000 a
week. It doesn't cost you anything to uh
be eligible for these prizes. All you
have to do is sign up to Blofin and
Bitbase in the pin comment and
description. For the Blofin ones, you
have to join my free Discord and follow
the instructions that are right here on
your screen in order to be eligible for
the giveaways. And of course, guys, make
sure to check out Antarctic
Decentralized Exchange. All these
exchanges, by the way, are giving you
very low VIP level 7 fees if you use my
link. You cannot find these deals
literally anywhere else. Also, guys, I'm
officially affiliated with client
funding, a crypto prop firm. If you're
interested in a prop firm, I have 15%
discounts on these funded accounts. That
is pretty much it for this video, guys.
This is what I'm looking for. This is
how I plan to trade on the macro high
time frames as well as the local time
frames. Make sure to like, subscribe,
click the bell for notifications. May
God bless everybody in the name of
Jesus, Yeshua, the Messiah. I pray you
and your family are super blessed. And I
will see everybody in the next video.